#### Kontakta

oscarhansson94@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/oscar-hansson-992a08199 (LinkedIn)

#### Främsta kompetenser

Windows
Telekommunikation
Devops

# Oscar Hansson

Systemutvecklare

Uppsala, Uppsala län, Sverige

# Sammanfattning

My name is Oscar Hansson and I am 29 years old. I recently got my bachelors degree in computer science at Stockholm university and I am currently employed att Sandvik coromant as a software developer. I am born and raised in Sweden but I have lived a couple of years in both Dublin and Barcelona.

### Erfarenhet

Sandvik Coromant Systemutvecklare augusti 2023 - Present (11 månader) Gimo

Releasy Customer Management Technical Support Agent februari 2020 - juli 2020 (6 månader) Barcelona, Catalonien, Spanien

ONE Contact Sales Specialist oktober 2019 - januari 2020 (4 månader) Barcelona, Catalonien, Spanien

DXC Technology Technical Support Specialist augusti 2018 - juni 2019 (11 månader) County Dublin, Ireland

# Utbildning

Stockholms universitet

Kandidatexamen, Datavetenskap · (augusti 2020 - maj 2023)

## Göteborgs universitet

Teknologie kandidatexamen (tekn.kand.), Datavetenskap · (augusti 2017 - januari 2018)

## Göteborgs universitet

Naturvetenskapligt basår · (augusti 2016 - maj 2017)